In this corner Grump!
I'm a grump!
In the other corner Not So Grump!
It's GameGrumps Versus!
*totally sick electric explosion noise*
*Cheering*
*Half-hearted clapping*
- Arin: Hi!
- Dan: Hey!
- Arin: Welcome to
Uhh...
- Dan: Mario Party
- Arin: *bad italian accent* Mario Paaty
- Dan: Which one is this?
- Arin: *bad italian accent, again* Eh Mario Paaty
It's Mario Party 10
- Dan: Woah, I've never played this one
- Arin, lying voice: Neither have I...
Just kidding, I played it on GrumpCade
You should watch that
- Dan: Did you really?
- Arin: Yep
- Dan: Oh, is this the one where fuckin Ross wouldn't hit a number?
And everyone was pissed off at him?
- Arin: No, that was, um...
Uhh..
- Dan: Another one
- Arin: Fortune Street
- Dan: Oh yeah
That is, that does
- Arin, interrupting: Although I'm sure something similar happened
in that one as well cause Ross is *literally* the worst
- Dan: Because Ross is Ross
- Arin: Umm, we're gonna play Mario Party
- Dan, cheerful: Yeah, let's do it man!
- Arin: Should be fun, cause I like these two
- Dan: We just can't stop doing Mario shit
- Arin: To proceed with this many players...
Oh fuck!
I can't use the game pad.
- Dan, sarcastically: You can't?
- Arin: Well then, I'm gonna have to
FUCK YOU, YOU FUCKING PIECE OF SHIT
GAMEPAD
-Dan: Woah woah, easy easy
-Arin: I'LL FUCKIN STAB YOU
-Dan: Ok, ok, I mean...
- Arin: I can use a, uhh, I can use this
alright, so we're good.